[{
    "question": "Which team won the 2015-2016 Premiere League?",
    "choice1": "Manchester United",
    "choice2": "Chelsea",
    "choice3": "Manchester City",
    "choice4": "Leicester City",
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "question": "Who had played for both Barcelona and Real Marid?",
    "choice1": "Johan Cruyff",
    "choice2": "Luis Enrique",
    "choice3": "Fabio Cannavaro",
    "choice4": "Nicolas Anelka",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "Which player had the most time winning Ballon'D Or?",
    "choice1": "Lionel Messi",
    "choice2": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    "choice3": "Ronaldinho",
    "choice4": "Pele",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League?",
    "choice1": "Sergio Aguero",
    "choice2": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    "choice3": "Sadio Mane",
    "choice4": "Thierry Henry",
    "answer": 3
}, {
    "question": "With 202 clean sheets, which goalkeeper has the best record in the Premier League?",
    "choice1": "Petr Cech",
    "choice2": "Peter Schmeichel",
    "choice3": "Edwin van de Sar",
    "choice4": "Alisson Becker",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "Which country won the first ever World Cup in 1930?",
    "choice1": "Uruguay",
    "choice2": "Brazil",
    "choice3": "England",
    "choice4": "Argentina",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "Which country has appeared in three World Cup finals, but never won the competition?",
    "choice1": "Croatia",
    "choice2": "Netherlands",
    "choice3": "Belgium",
    "choice4": "Argentina",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "The record number of World Cup goals is 16, scored by who?",
    "choice1": "Miroslav Klose",
    "choice2": "Pele",
    "choice3": "Gerd Muller",
    "choice4": "Diego Maradona",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "What was Messi's schoolboy team?",
    "choice1": "Santos",
    "choice2": "Newell's Old Boys",
    "choice3": "Sporting CB",
    "choice4": "Boca Juniors",
    "answer": 2
}, {
    "question": "Which club has won the most Champions League titles?",
    "choice1": "Barcelona",
    "choice2": "AC Milan",
    "choice3": "Real Madrid",
    "choice4": "Liverpool",
    "answer": 3
}, {
    "question": "Which country won the first ever World Cup in 1930?",
    "choice1": "Uruguay",
    "choice2": "Brazil",
    "choice3": "England",
    "choice4": "Argentina",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "Who is the only player to win the Champions League with three different clubs?",
    "choice1": "David Beckham",
    "choice2": "Zinedine Zidane",
    "choice3": "Paolo Maldini",
    "choice4": "Clarence Seedorf",
    "answer": 4
}, {
    "question": "Who is the Champions League's top goalscorer of all time?",
    "choice1": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    "choice2": "Lionel Messi",
    "choice3": "Gerd Muller",
    "choice4": "Lewandowski",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "The Euro 2000 final between France and Italy was decided by Golden Goal. Which player scored the goal?",
    "choice1": "David Trezeguet",
    "choice2": "Michel Platini",
    "choice3": "Claude Makelele",
    "choice4": "Laurent Blanc",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "Who holds the record age for youngest head coach in the Bundesliga is 28 years and 205 days?",
    "choice1": "Jurgen Klopp",
    "choice2": "Thomas Tuchel",
    "choice3": "Julian Nagelsmann",
    "choice4": "Mark van Bommel",
    "answer": 3
}, {
    "question": "Which manager was famously said to have given players 'the Hairdryer Treatment'?",
    "choice1": "Sir Alex Ferguson",
    "choice2": "Arsene Wenger",
    "choice3": "Jose Mourinho",
    "choice4": "Pep Guardiola",
    "answer": 1
}, {
    "question": "I was the first Liverpool player to win the Ballon d'Or. Who am I?",
    "choice1": "Steven Gerrald",
    "choice2": "Michael Owen",
    "choice3": "Phil Neal",
    "choice4": "Alan Kennedy",
    "answer": 2
}]